

LUYEN QUANG DUC

CONTENT MARKETING

CONTACT

- 0702012186
- luyenquangduc1995@gmail.com
- HCM City, Viet Nam

EDUCATION

OPEN UNIVERSITY

MAJOR: MANAGEMENT INFORMATION SYSTEM NOV 2013 - JUNE 2017

SKILLS

Management Marketing Planning **Analysis** Research Social Branding Creativity Communitation Team work Presentation Adobe Photoshop Adobe Premiere Adobe Lightroom

ABOUT

Find opportunities and challenges in my career, orient myself to become a professional brand marketer. I want an environment where it can fully exploit my abilities and strengths, so that I can contribute my own value to the company. Since then, I have been able to develop and connect the best experiences and values for our customers and bring the brand further thanks to the best quality and service that cannot be compared with anywhere else. And I like working under pressure because it can only make us grow and grow better day by day.

WORK EXPERIENCE

MARKETING EXECUTIVE

VNG CORPORATION: NOV 2016 - MARCH 2017 Developing Brand Strategy about Game (Phong Van 3D):

- Research, planning and implementation
- Create creative ideas to promote a game and company's brand.
- Operate and manage online/offline marketing activities.
- Measuring the efficiency, analyze data and quality of work from which to make accurate decisions.
 - Develop and create relationships with KOL and influencer.
 - **Event organization**

CONTENT MARKETING EXECUTIVE

CREATORY: MAY 2018 - MAY 2019

Developing strategy, identity and brand name of influencer (Win.D, Oops Buron)

- Project owner.
- Training and brand image orientation for influencers.
- Data analysis and measurement from different platforms (Facebook, Youtube,...)
- Working closely with client, agency, PR.
- Filming, editing and producing videos.
- Design and create creative content.
- Planning, running and mataining Facebook Ads.
- Tracking and adjusting strategies are always relevant to the market. Tracking competitors, understand the market and the fan/customers
- Event organization.
- Builling new concept for developing brand image of influencers based on insight and behavior of the fan/customer.
- Copywriter: Write creative script to promote product and viral Video/TVC.
- Market survey.



LUYEN QUANG DUC

CONTENT MARKETING

INTERESTS

Soccer Music Game Brand advertising Reading book

SOFT SKILLS

Negotiation
Time management
Problem solving
Strategic thinking
Group working
Work independently

HONOR & REWARDS

- Best associate commitee: 2014 2017
- Best event coordinator of information technology faculty: 2014 2017
- Employee of month in VNG about marketing:
 Dec 2016 Jan 2017
- 1st in making film about creatory company: Nov 2018 - Dec 2018

REFERENCE

NGUYEN HUU LOI

HEAD OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY FACULTY

EMAIL: loinguyenhuu.it@gmail.com

Mobile: 01204767739

PHAN VIET TINH

DATA ANALYSIS AND CONTENT MARKETER OF VNG

Email: pvtinh48@gmail.com

Mobile: 0963854814

DANG TUYET MAI

GAME MANAGER OF CREATORY

Email: mai@creatory.vn Mobile: 0902992691

PORTFOLIO

https://luyenquangduc.github.io/lqd.github.io/